{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What is the name of our cohort?",
  correct_answer: "Dan, stop eating the internet!",
  incorrect_answers: ["Dan","Stop eating the internet, Dan!","040119"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What is the biggest threat to the internet?",
  correct_answer: "Dan",
  incorrect_answers: ["Sharks","Coffee","Earthquakes"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who bought the first snacks?",
  correct_answer: "Troy",
  incorrect_answers: ["Danielle","Ferris","Kevin"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who are you?",
  correct_answer: "Dan",
  incorrect_answers: ["Dan","Dan","Dan"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who likes cottage cheese?",
  correct_answer: "Ali",
  incorrect_answers: ["Grandmas","Mothers","Sebastian"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who was our Mod 1 instructor?",
  correct_answer: "Alex",
  incorrect_answers: ["Tashawn","Jeff","Tim"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who was our Mod 2 instructor?",
  correct_answer: "Tashawn",
  incorrect_answers: ["Ferris","Evans","Tim"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who was our Mod 3 instructor?",
  correct_answer: "Evans",
  incorrect_answers: ["Tim","Alex","Will"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who was our Mod 4 instructor?",
  correct_answer: "Tim",
  incorrect_answers: ["Alex","God","Tashawn"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who bought the beers when the keg was broken?",
  correct_answer: "Ferris",
  incorrect_answers: ["Troy","Kevin","WeWork"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who makes things harder for himself?",
  correct_answer: "Jeff",
  incorrect_answers: ["Jeff","Jeff","Jeff"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What painter does Sebastian love?",
  correct_answer: "Bob Ross",
  incorrect_answers: ["Vincent Van Gogh","Claude Monet","Ali the Great"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who got accepted into NYU?",
  correct_answer: "Sarah",
  incorrect_answers: ["Woohoo","Congrats","Woot woot"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who can speak backwards?",
  correct_answer: "Mom",
  incorrect_answers: ["Ali","Grandma","Yoda"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "When did we get chairs?",
  correct_answer: "When we took them",
  incorrect_answers: ["Mod 4","Too late","Never got a chair"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What do the coffee cups say?",
  correct_answer: "Always do what you love wework",
  incorrect_answers: ["Flatiron School is amazing","learn love code","Always coding, never quitting"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Whatâ€™s the Flatiron School slogan?",
  correct_answer: "learn love code",
  incorrect_answers: ["If you're not first, you're last","It's all a turing test","Stress out for no reason!"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "How many mods are there?",
  correct_answer: "5",
  incorrect_answers: ["8","1","Dan"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "How do you feel about sushi saga?",
  correct_answer: "Sebastian is a madman",
  incorrect_answers: ["Hate it!","Love it!","It was fine."]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Which programming language is the best?",
  correct_answer: "HTML",
  incorrect_answers: ["Ruby","JavaScript","CSS"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What will you do after Flatiron School?",
  correct_answer: "Die",
  incorrect_answers: ["Get a job","Continue learning forever","Live at Flatiron School until they kick me out"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Which mod was your favorite?",
  correct_answer: "Mod 4",
  incorrect_answers: ["Mod 3","Mod 2","Mod 1"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What did Edgar, Danielle, Ferris, and Troy win at the OpenSource ERPs Hackathon?",
  correct_answer: "Most diverse team and unique idea",
  incorrect_answers: ["A big piece of cardboard","They won something?","Unclear"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "How many women are in our cohort?",
  correct_answer: "5",
  incorrect_answers: ["10","2","4"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What game is played by our cohort most often at happy hours?",
  correct_answer: "Stack cup",
  incorrect_answers: ["Slap cup","Beer pong","Rugby"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Bubble tea?",
  correct_answer: "Bubble tea",
  incorrect_answers: ["Bubble tea","Bubble","Tea"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Why Flatiron School?",
  correct_answer: "It's the best",
  incorrect_answers: ["It's so cheap","It's easy","Everyone is very serious here"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Why do we write and present blog posts?",
  correct_answer: "For funsies",
  incorrect_answers: ["Because we have to","To create an online presence","Torture"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Why are we here?",
  correct_answer: "42",
  incorrect_answers: ["To learn, love, and code","For the community happy hours","Dan"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who is your mom?",
  correct_answer: "Ali",
  incorrect_answers: ["Ali","Ali","Sebastian"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who are the best TCFs?",
  correct_answer: "Ali & Sebastian",
  incorrect_answers: ["Jeff & Dan","Ferris & Danielle","Rob & Kevin"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who has pink hair and just got a hair cut?",
  correct_answer: "Danielle",
  incorrect_answers: ["Edgar","Dan","Soyeong"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Why is Flatiron School in FiDi?",
  correct_answer: "What are you talking about? We're in the Flatiron district right now.",
  incorrect_answers: ["Something about flat irons","FiDi is beautiful and we love it here","The Flatiron building is full"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Statue of Liberty?",
  correct_answer: "NO",
  incorrect_answers: ["Nah","Not today","No thank you"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Are you going to Game Jam?",
  correct_answer: "Yep",
  incorrect_answers: ["Yes","Yeah","Probably"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who does Tashawn hate?",
  correct_answer: "Drake",
  incorrect_answers: ["Sebastian","Ali","Jeff"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "Who is the most powerful instructor?",
  correct_answer: "Evans",
  incorrect_answers: ["Not Evans","Probably Evans","Idk"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "What would you do differently if you had to repeat your time at Flatiron School?",
  correct_answer: "Steal chairs earlier",
  incorrect_answers: ["Work harder","Be more lazy","Study more"]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
{
  category: "Dan",
  question: "",
  correct_answer: "",
  incorrect_answers: ["","",""]
}
